William Hall

Phone: (803)414-9580 | E-mail: <u>WHall22@outlook.com</u>

Professional Summary

Successful graduate of Midlands Technical College with an Associates in Computer Technology and recipient of the TechHire Front End Programming Scholarship. Six years of customer service. Passionate about building positive customer experiences with intuitive designs.

Technical Skills

Programming: Java, MySQL, HTML, CSS Advanced, JavaScript, AJAX, Bootstrap 4

Software: Microsoft Office 365, Adobe Photoshop, GIMP, Visual Studio, Coldfusion Builder

Operating Systems: Windows 7/8.1/10, Ubuntu Linux, Android, IOS

Work Experience

Department of Education, Columbia, SC UX/UI Developer

August 2019 – Present

- Designing styling guide used for website and web application standards.
- Communicating with team members in daily SCRUM sessions.

DDI Technology, Lexington, SC Customer Service Representative I

July 2019 – August 2019

- Trained and supported customers using electronic vehicle registration software.
- Managed work items using ticket manager system to ensure issues are solved.

Department of Health and Human Services, Columbia, SC May 2019 – July 2019 **IT Specialist**

- Provided software support in an enterprise setting of 1000+ employees.
- Ensured high level of security with multi-factor authentication based on HIPAA regulations.

116 Wine and Espresso, Columbia, SC

June 2018 – April 2019

- Bartender/Manager
- Created a unique experience for all guests with an unmatched level of customer service.
- Managed all monetary transactions throughout establishment.

Thirsty Fellow, Columbia, SC

November 2013 – June 2018

Waiter

- Excelled at developing relationships with customers and creating repeat business.
- Voted best waiter in Columbia by Free Times 2014.

Education

Midlands Technical College, Columbia, SC

Associate of Applied Science in Computer Technology Aug. 2017 – May. 2019

TechHire Front End Programming Scholarship May 2019 – Aug. 2019

University of South Carolina, Columbia, SC

Bachelor of Science in Information Science Expected Graduation May 2021